<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>STC-Rec</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on STC-Rec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 10:27:13 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 10:27:13 -0600</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>The STC Recreational Program was established in 1976. It is a nonprofit organization and is supported by the taxpayers of Tama and Toledo. STC REC is available to all youth in grades K-8 (depending on the sport) within the STC School District. The REC program strives to improve program availability, facilities, and equipment. Some past improvements include: adding a batting cage, scoreboards, and fencing improvements. STC REC is managed by a board of seven member/volunteers who meet regularly.</description></item><item><title>Schedules</title><link>/schedules/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:47:34 -0600</pubDate><guid>/schedules/</guid><description>Schedules will be updated on a seasonal basis.
Attachments Open or download the 2024 June Summer REC Schedule: 2024 Summer REC Schedule</description></item><item><title>Bus Schedule for Summer Rec</title><link>/bus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:39:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>/bus/</guid><description>Sorry, STC Rec can no longer offer bus transportation in the summer months.</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>/registration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:37:02 -0600</pubDate><guid>/registration/</guid><description>Forms can be downloaded, printed, filled, and mailed to:
STC Rec Programs PO Box 271 Toledo, IA 52342 Or, you may save postage and drop completed forms off at either the STC Elementary office or STC Middle School office.
You also have the option to register online this year at http://getmeregistered.com/stcrecSummer, and there are NO added fees for credit card payments!
NOTE: If you are registering a child for multiple sports or registering more than one child at a time, scroll to the bottom of the http://getmeregistered.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:20:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description> Coaches: Check back later for more information.
REC Board Members: Name Role Phone Email Chelsea Ahrens Board President Cellular: 641-481-5112 cahrens@s-tama.k12.ia.us Claire Mayo Board Secretary Cellular: 563-321-8961 clairemgraves@gmail.com Lindsay Schumacher Treasurer Cellular: 319-461-3755 lschumacher@lattaharris.com Ashley Raue Board Member Cellular: 641-485-0187 araue@s-tama.k12.ia.us Jenny Schlabaugh Board Member Cellular: 641-751-4504 cjschlabaugh@gmail.com Tolly Van Dyke Board Member Cellular: 641-751-7897 vandyke2232@yahoo.com Deanna Zmolek Board Member Cellular: 641-485-2710 dzmolek@s-tama.k12.ia.us</description></item><item><title>T-ball, Baseball, and Softball Registration Deadline</title><link>/event/2020/april10/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/event/2020/april10/</guid><description>A downloadable registration form can be found at Registration page .</description></item></channel></rss>